<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Jobs4SMCYouth</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="nav_job_post">Job Posting</string>
    <string name="nav_scholarships">Scholarships</string>
    <string name="nav_transportation">Transportation</string>
    <string name="nav_requirements">Requirements</string>
    <string name="nav_success_stories">Success Stories</string>
    <string name="nav_about">About</string>
    <string name="nav_print">Print</string>
    <string name="nav_job_prep">Job Prep</string>
    <string name="nav_applications">Applications</string>
    <string name="nav_interview">Interview</string>
    <string name="nav_resume_cover_letters">Resume/Cover Letters</string>
    <string name="nav_job_search_sites">Job Search Websites</string>
    <string name="nav_tips">Tips</string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about_j4y">Jobs for Youth is a year-round program designed to help young people who live in San Mateo County develop their job search skills. The program provides employment services to all youth between the ages of 14-21 years old at no cost to them or to employers. There are no eligibility requirements to join this program. Services are available to all youth regardless of socio-economic or risk level.</string>
    <string name="about_services">Job placement assistance (job referrals)\n\n One-on-one job counseling \n\n Job preparation workshops that cover: 1.) mastering job application forms; 2.) interviewing skills; 3.) resume writing assistance; and 4.) job search websites for teens \n\n All interested youth must contact their nearest Jobs for Youth office to sign up and attend a job preparation workshop. Jobs for Youth staff can also provide presentations/job preparation workshops at the local high schools. If interested, please contact your nearest location and speak to a Jobs for Youth Specialist.</string>
    <string name="interview_during">\u2022 Smile and Introduce yourself.\n\n\u2022 Give the employer a firm handshake at the beginning of the interview.\n\n\u2022 Make eye contact and have good posture.\n\n\u2022 Only say good things to the employer (even if you hated your first job).\n\n\u2022 Answer questions with examples. Refer to a story to show the example.\n\n\u2022 Speak clearly and slowly; speak loud enough to be heard.\n\n\u2022 If you don’t understand a question, ask for clarification.\n\n\u2022 Do not discuss pay (unless they ask).\n\n\u2022 You must ask questions at the end of the interview. A few easy ones are:\nWhat is the schedule for this position? Is it flexible?\nCould you describe a typical day (or week) for this job?\nIs there a dress code?\n\n\u2022 At the end of the interview, give the employer a firm handshake, smile, get a card/contact info, and thank him/her.</string>
    <string name="interview_before">\u2022 Eat something before your interview.\n\n\u2022 Learn about the company you are applying to. A great way to do this is by reviewing the company\'s website.\n\n\u2022 Practice answering interview questions with friends or family.\n\n\u2022 View mock interviews on YouTube or other websites.\n\n\u2022 Review your application and resume.\n\n\u2022 Prepare copies of your resume to give to the interviewer.\n\n\u2022 Do not bring food in the interview room.\n\n\u2022 Do not reschedule the interview, unless an emergency happens.\n\n\u2022 Arrive 10-15 minutes early to your interview. Make sure to give yourself ample time for parking, traffic, public transportation, rides from others, and/or childcare).\n\n\u2022 Call in advance if you will be running late (note that this may hurt your chances of getting the job).</string>
    <string name="interview_after">\u2022 Email the employer a thank you letter right after you interview.\n\n\u2022 Follow up with the employer for the status of your interview. If they have given you a specific date to follow up, contact the employer on that date. If no date was given, rule of thumb is to wait at least 4-5 business days before following up.</string>

    <string-array name="jobTitle">
        <item>Food Pantry Staff</item>
        <item>Cashiers and Cooks</item>
        <item>Helper</item>
        <item>General Labor</item>
        <item>Swim Instructor</item>
        <item>Volunteer/Assistant Activity</item>
        <item>Customer Service/ Clean up</item>
        <item>Customer Service Associate</item>
        <item>Clerical Assistant/Receptionist</item>
        <item>Line Prep</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="city">
        <item>Daly City</item>
        <item>Daly City</item>
        <item>Burlingame</item>
        <item>South San Francisco</item>
        <item>Pacifica</item>
        <item>Daly City</item>
        <item>Pacifica</item>
        <item>Half Moon Bay</item>
        <item>Half Moon Bay</item>
        <item>Pacifica</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="duties">
        <item>Fill all requests for groceries, sort and store donated food items, maintenance of food items.</item>
        <item>N/A</item>
        <item>N/A</item>
        <item>General labor in manufacturing plant.</item>
        <item>N/A</item>
        <item>N/A</item>
        <item>Work at bakery.</item>
        <item>Greet and assist customers, restock, clean and maintain store.</item>
        <item>Receptionist work, comput work ,greeting people, answering phones.</item>
        <item>Customer service, food preparation, cashier, cleaning, restocking, dish-washing, shop.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="payRate">
        <item>$10/hr</item>
        <item>$10.75/hr</item>
        <item>$12.50/hr</item>
        <item>TBD</item>
        <item>$16/hr</item>
        <item>$11/hr</item>
        <item>$10/hr</item>
        <item>$12/hr</item>
        <item>$10/hr</item>
        <item>$12.25/hr</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="age">
        <item>16+ years old</item>
        <item>18+ years old</item>
        <item>18+ years old</item>
        <item>18+ years old</item>
        <item>17+ years old</item>
        <item>18+ years old</item>
        <item>16+ years old</item>
        <item>17+ years old</item>
        <item>16+ years old</item>
        <item>14+ years old</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="success_story">
        <item>Edgar Aguirre has a passion in his life: to dance. When he was four years old, his family emigrated from Guatemala. He is now a senior at Sequoia High school, a leader in the AVID (Advancement Via Individual Determination) Program, a former member of the Key Club and the Canada College Upward Bound program, a member and leader of Sequoia High School’s Advanced Dance program, who has been accepted to a prestigious dance program in Southern California, and who’s eyes are set on  Chapman University. In addition to being an outstanding dancer and scholar, Edgar is involved in his church community, coordinating childcare services and co-teaching first through fifth grade students. Additionally, Edgar has been volunteering at the Dance Arts Center as a buddy and guide, working with special needs children who have an interest in the performing arts. Edgar plans to use this scholarship money to assist him with the expenses of attending college.</item>
        <item>Flor Aquino Ortiz is a native Spanish speaker, and was not designated fluent in English until 2011, last semester she successfully achieved a 4.0 GPA.  Her father is working to support her, her mother and her siblings and her parents’ struggles have greatly influenced her to become a first generation college student. Flor is a member of Woodside High School’s Green Academy, a part of the Forestry Club, participating in the California Forestry Challenge in Santa Cruz and a co-founder of College Track’s Dreamer’s Club, an organization that addresses and supports the needs of the undocumented. She has won College Track’s Tenacity Award and earned a space on Woodside’s Honor Roll. Additionally, Flor has volunteered as a soccer coach for the Ravenswood Athletic Association for the last seven years, helping six to nine year old girls improve, not only in soccer, but emotionally and academically. She plans to use this scholarship to help with the financial costs of college.</item>
        <item>Grisell Canas grew up in Mexico, and came to this country with her mother and brother seven years ago. When she arrived and started the 6th grade, she spoke no English, she now has a 3.31 GPA taking International Baccalaureate courses and is enrolled in Sequoia’s Health Careers Academy. Because of the difficulties she encountered as an immigrant, Grisell decided to become a Biology tutor at Sequoia, during her junior year, then, during her senior year, she has been tutoring elementary school youth, helping them with Math and English homework, reading and English skills because they, like she once was, were in need of help. Because she is an undocumented student she will not qualify for Federal funding, this scholarship money will help her realize her dream of becoming an attorney, an immigration lawyer to help those most in need fight for their rights.</item>
        <item>Jennifer Castro’s parents came from Mexico to make a better life for their daughter, through their example and her determination, she will reach her goal of attending a four year university. Jennifer is a member of both AVID (Advancement Via Individual Determination) class and the Upward Bound program, which provides guidance to low income students who aspire to become the first to attend college. While at Sequoia High School she became a member of the STEM club-Science Superheroes who teach second and third graders about science, and an office in the Latino Student Union, where she developed her leadership skills. Jennifer hopes to attend a four year university and study Psychology, integrating American Sign Language which she is studying, to become an art therapist.</item>
        <item>Jennifer Cuevas has two siblings that are already attending college, and though her parents are supportive of their children’s goals, financially, it is impossible to support all three. As an active Trio Upward bound program and AVID participant, Jennifer has been recognized as a student on the Principal’s Honor List for her 4.0 GPA during the last three semesters. Additionally, she is vice president of the volunteering on campus (the Octagon Club), a former member of the lacrosse team, and a volunteer at Kids in Partnership (KIP), a program focused on helping elementary students who are at risk. Jennifer’s end goal is to become a Pediatrician at Kaiser Permanente.</item>
        <item>Marie Barbara Estacio is a member of TRiO-student Support Services Program at Skyline College. This program is designed to provide educational opportunities for first-generation, low-income students who seek degrees from four year institutions. Marie has managed multiple jobs while managing a full class schedule of 12 units, earning a 3.5 GPA last semester. After her family emigrated from the Philippines in 2006, Marie’s mother had to spend the majority of her time working to support the family, leaving less time to celebrate the achievements of her daughter. Her mother’s perseverance has inspired Marie to set out on a path to obtain first her Paralegal Degree, then a Bachelor’s degree in Political Science, and finally attend law school.</item>
        <item>Lluvia Garnica states “she never felt like a minority” until she attended Sequoia High School, where she now had classmates of different races. This forced her to step out of her comfort zone and join both TRIO Upward Bound and AVID-two programs that support first generation college bound student. Lluvia has a 4.029 cumulative GPA while taking a rigorous course load. She is co-president of the Latino Student Union, a volunteer at Project Read since 2012, helping students who are new to the English language, as she once was. Additionally, she volunteers at the Boys and Girls Club, mentoring 15 second graders, helping them with their homework. Lluvia’s dream is to become a Psychologist and return to help her community.</item>
        <item>Christopher Gonzalez comes from a single parent family. His mother works most of the day to support him and his siblings, and Chris contributes as he can, all the while maintaining a 3.0 grade point average despite having an Individualized Education Plan. He has been on the Honor role for academic achievement at Jefferson High School several times and also was a teacher’s assistant in his Social Communication class, where he assisted those in needed. Chris took a Guest Service Class at Skyline College with a food service goal in mind and now he wants to continue his education at Skyline and take more food service classes with the goal of one day opening his own food truck or a restaurant. Additionally, Chris has volunteered in a program called S.L.A.M. that goes around assisting homeless shelters and food banks.</item>
        <item>Samrawit Keleta, known as Sammy, plans to major in nursing, not because she couldn’t become a doctor, but because nurses interact with, and help people. Sammy’s parents emigrated from Eritrea when they were 16; she will be the first in her family to graduate high school and continue on to college. In addition to being hard working and self-motivating in her classwork, Sammy has a resume of volunteer and extracurricular activities that is impressive. She is a 4 year member of Exploratory Experiences Program, where she went to Washington D.C. in 2012, as a part of Close Up Foundation’ s educational tours, a member of College Track in East Palo Alto, and is active in mentoring and tutoring students at Menlo Atherton, as well as dance and basketball. In the summer of 2014, Sammy went to Triavolo Village, Asmara, Eritrea to volunteer in a hospital, but because she couldn’t get certified, she started a day camp for the children of the village, playing soccer in the mornings, and teaching them how to read and write English in the afternoon.</item>
        <item>Yunuen Alejandra Lopez Garcia came to this country from Mexico, with her parents, when she was 8 years old, not speaking English. She will be the first person in her family to attend a four year University, graduate and see the world beyond the boundaries of East Palo Alto. In addition to helping her family, translating for them, caring for her siblings and becoming a shining star in Menlo Atherton’s AVID (Advancement Via Individual Determination) Yunuen , with all that is going on in her life, also has the time and energy to help and inspire others by assisting other students with advice and help and by starting and leading the DREAMer Club at College Track. She depends on DACA and the California Dream Act funds to afford her college.</item>
        <item>Ana Martinez-Gomez has a dream to become a veterinarian, and she is taking the necessary steps to achieve that end. As a member of Carlmont’s Business Technology Academy, she was honored last semester with the Academy’s Role model Award. Because of her family’s inability to provide financial expenses, Ana applied and was chosen to intern last summer with the Metropolitan Transportation Commission at San Carlos Public Works Dept. to earn funds to pay for her school and graduation expenses. She has volunteered with both the SPCA and Peninsula Humane Society and, in addition to her role as “Dog TLC Volunteer”, she is a member of the Show Choir program, performing choreographed singing and dancing routines at school choir concerts. She will be the first of her family to attend college.</item>
        <item>Eve McNally is one on five siblings raised in a single parent family who is also captain of her schools water polo team, that are ranked number one in their division. In addition to being a magnificent, positive athletic role model, Eve is an inspiration both in athletics, in the classroom, and in Life. She has earned a 3.80 GPA while enrolling in Aragon’s most demanding classes, while tutoring and mentoring academically challenged students in the guided studies program.  Eve also started Picking for Hunger(P4H), as student network dedicated to finding home owners who had excess fruit to be picked and then donated to those in need through CALL , a distribution network. Through her organizational skills and determination P4H became recognized as an official club at Aragon High School. Eve’s goal is to assist people facing economic hardships, to unsure this, she plans on majoring in Sociology at UC Berkeley, and will use the scholarship to offset the costs of her education.</item>
        <item>Giselle Mendoza is the first in her family to attend college, both CSM and U C Santa Cruz, and she is doing it as a single mother. She has a determination to build a better life for herself, her daughter, and her community. Giselle is currently participating in an internship with South San Francisco Adult probation, and has an impressive volunteer resume: Coastside Collaborative, Youth Leadership Institute, Half Moon Bay Community Center, Police Activities League, Sherriff’s Activities League, the Senior Center and El Centro in Half moon Bay and numerous other organizations. She is now attending UC Santa Cruz and pursuing two BA degrees and will use this scholarship money to help with her scholastic finances.</item>
        <item>Janah May T. Oclaman has only recently immigrated to the USA from Philippines, but she brought with her a love for learning and a level of commitment that will enable her to develop into anything she chooses. She graduated from Our Lady of the Holy Rosary School, Rosaryville Compound, Mulawin, Tanza, Cavite as the class Valedictorian. While in school she was involved in the School’s outreach program for the less privileged members of the community helping student, read write and solve math problems in addition to the Donate a book, and Fund Drives for typhoon victims. This was accomplished despite multiple medical problems and less than ideal family life. Janah May is currently going to College of San Mateo, working on her associate degree, and planning on transferring to Stanford to work on a BS in Neurobiology. </item>
        <item>Janae Peats is attending Bennett College in Greensboro, North Carolina, an all girl’s historically black college. Upon graduation she will pursue a master’s degree in public policy and intends to apply for a fellowship with the League of Woman Voters of California. She recently presented an academic piece at the annual Sigma Tau Delta Convention, an International English Honors Society, in New Mexico this year. In addition to her academic achievements, Janae is insistent about helping her peers have a successful college experience, just as she was when assisting at College Track in East Palo Alto, where she served as a College Track Senator. Janae is dependent on scholarships and financial aid to further her college ambitions and will use this scholarship to offset her ongoing expenses. Additionally, Janae was selected to the Pearson Student Advisory Board and, as a NC Voter Defender, developed strategies with the Student Government Association to register students at Bennett College to vote. Janae currently dedicates a great deal of her time to raising the minimum wage in the #FightFor15.</item>
        <item>Bryce Addison Rodgers is an exceptional student at Menlo Atherton High School; he is an honor student, a star football player, a leading thrower on the track team and a principle member of the Black Student Union, where he is a leader and mentor to other youth, both on and off the field. When he was younger, he participated in a scouting club called “Pathfinders” who’s mission was “Service to our fellow man , he continues to do that today. Currently Bryce works each summer and saves his money for his college dream: to attend UCLA and get a Masters of Business Administration Degree.</item>
        <item>Angelica Russell is a graduate of the Transitional Housing Plus Program of Star Vista Transitional Youth Services where she is still an active participant and mentor. Angel’s challenges have become opportunities for personal growth and professional development. She is co-chair of the Foster Youth Advisory Board, advising the Human Services Agency of San Mateo County; she is a Bay Area Policy Intern with California Youth Connection, and a full time student at City College of San Francisco. The barriers that she has had to overcome have inspired her to work for a better foster youth system. To achieve this end, she will be transferring to San Francisco State to obtain Degree in Social Work. Angelica will use the money from this scholarship to defray the costs of her education.</item>
        <item>Natasha Stibor continually excelled in both academics and athletics, all the while working part time to support herself financially. She continues to do this while attending the University of Massachusetts in Boston and participating on their NCAA Woman’s Soccer Team. Natasha is a Marketing Management Major at UMass Boston who wants to pursue a career in advertising and marketing.</item>
        <item>Zakiya Williams is a former foster youth, and  alumni of the Transitional Housing Plus Program of Star Vista who is working full time, attending Skyline College, who still has the time and energy to return the  gifts she has received, to her community. In her sophomore year at Skyline, she has applied to both Cal State Hayward and San Francisco State so she can realize her dream of becoming a probation Officer.  In addition to a paid summer internship at Human Resources Dept. of San Mateo County in Redwood City, she also volunteered at My New Red Shoes, an organization that provides new shoes and clothing for underprivileged youth. Zakiya’s perseverance serves as an example that one does not have to be defined by one’s past experiences.</item>
        <item>Sawleha  Zubair immigrated to the United States from South Africa 1998 with her family. In 2010 her father suffered a major heart attack while on a pilgrimage to Saudi Arabia, which left her mother as the sole support of the family and her other three siblings. Sawleha hopes to be the second of her family to attend college and plans to become a lawyer to fight for the rights of those who are the victims of racism and discrimination, something she has experienced in her own life. While attending F.A.M.E. in San Francisco, Sawleha is the president of “ Feed the Homeless” club, which distributes lunches for those without permanent food and shelter, she is also president of the drama club and  plays on the school varsity basketball team, all while maintaining a GPA of 3.8.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="success_name">
        <item>Edgar Aguirre</item>
        <item>Flor Aquino Ortiz</item>
        <item>Grisell Canas</item>
        <item>Jennifer Castro</item>
        <item>Jennifer Cuevas</item>
        <item>Marie Barbara Estacio</item>
        <item>Lluvia Garnica</item>
        <item>Christopher Gonzalez</item>
        <item>Samrawit Keleta</item>
        <item>Yunuen Alejandra Lopez Garcia</item>
        <item>Ana Martinez-Gomez</item>
        <item>Eve McNally</item>
        <item>Giselle Mendoza</item>
        <item>Janah May T. Oclaman</item>
        <item>Janae Peats</item>
        <item>Bryce Addison Rodgers</item>
        <item>Angelica Russell</item>
        <item>Natasha Stibor</item>
        <item>Zakiya Williams</item>
        <item>Sawleha  Zubair</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="print">Print</string>
    <string name="print_settings">PRINT SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="printing_help">PRINTING HELP</string>
    <string name="print_plugin_manager">Print Plugin Manager</string>
    <string name="print_plugin_manager_description">Help users install their printers PSP</string>
    <string name="print_help_menu">Print Help Menu</string>
    <string name="print_help_menu_description">Provide help content within your application</string>
    <string name="custom_data_title">Please enter the custom data below</string>
    <string name="custom_data_tag">Tag</string>
    <string name="custom_data_value">Value</string>
    <string name="asset">Asset</string>
    <string name="layout_option">PAGE LAYOUT</string>
    <string name="layout_center">Center</string>
    <string name="layout_center_top">Center Top</string>
    <string name="layout_crop">Fill</string>
    <string name="layout_fit">Fit</string>
    <string name="layout_top_left">Top Left</string>
    <string name="margin_option">PAGE MARGINS</string>
    <string name="layout_with_margin">1/2 Inch</string>
    <string name="layout_without_margin">None</string>
    <string name="layout_with_top_margin">Top Only</string>
    <string name="metrics_option">METRICS</string>
    <string name="unique_device_id_per_app">UNIQUE DEVICE ID</string>
    <string name="content_option">CONTENT TYPE</string>
    <string name="content_pdf">PDF</string>
    <string name="content_image">Image</string>
    <string name="lib_font">fonts/HPSimplified_Rg.ttf</string>
    <string name="add_constom_data">Add Data</string>
    <string name="not_encrypted">Not Encrypted</string>
    <string name="unique_per_app">Unique Per App</string>
    <string name="unique_per_vendor">Unique Per Vendor</string>
    <string name="select_a_file">SELECT A FILE</string>
    <string name="file_selected">File Selected</string>
    <string name="transportation"><![CDATA[The program can assist active participants with bus tickets to get to and from job related activities. For more information and to have the private online document shared with you, please contact <b><a href="jobs4smcyouth@gmail.com">Jobs for Youth</a></b>]]></string>

</resources>
